Guide to the Red Lodge Canning Company Records 1922-1974
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Correspondence, 1924-1974; Series I; 58.25 linear feet
  - General Correspondence, 1924-1974; Subseries 1; 56.0 linear feet
    - Colorado Public Utilities Commission, 1950 (Box-folder 73/1)
    - Crane Company, 1950 (Box-folder 73/2)
    - Kenneth Curtis, 1950 (Box-folder 73/3)
    - C, 1950 (Box-folder 73/4)
    - Elks, 1950 (Box-folder 73/5)
    - D-E, 1950 (Box-folder 73/6)
    - Jay G. Feldstein and Company, 1950 (Box-folder 73/7)
    - Food Machinery Corporation, 1950 (Box-folder 73/8)
    - F, 1950 (Box-folder 73/9)
    - G, 1950 (Box-folder 73/10)
    - H, 1950 (Box-folder 73/11)
    - I, 1950 (Box-folder 73/12)
    - J, 1950 (Box-folder 73/13)
    - Kelley How Thompson Company, 1950 (Box-folder 73/14)
    - K, 1950 (Box-folder 73/15)
    - L, 1950 (Box-folder 73/16)
    - B. W. Mann, 1950 (Box-folder 74/1)
    - Meinrath Brokerage Company, 1950 (Box-folder 74/2)
    - Montana, 1950 (Box-folder 74/3)
    - Montana Chamber of Commerce, 1950 (Box-folder 74/4)
    - M, 1950 (Box-folder 74/5)
    - N, 1950 (Box-folder 74/6)
    - O-P, 1950 (Box-folder 74/7)
    - Regent Can Food Company (Safeway Stores), 1950 (Box-folder 74/8)
    - R, 1950 (Box-folder 74/9)
    - Max Schmidt, 1950 (Box-folder 74/10)
    - Alden Smith, 1950 (Box-folder 74/11)
    - Stone Hall Company, 1950 (Box-folder 74/12)
    - George L. Tracy Company Billings, 1950 (Box-folder 74/13)
    - George L. Tracy Company Butte, 1950 (Box-folder 74/14)
    - George L. Tracy Company Great Falls, 1950 (Box-folder 75/1)
    - George L. Tracy Company Great Falls, 1950 (Box-folder 75/2)
    - S-T, 1950 (Box-folder 75/3)
    - U-V, 1950 (Box-folder 75/4)
    - Wyoming, 1950 (Box-folder 75/5)
    - W-Y, 1950 (Box-folder 75/6)
    - American Can Company, 1951 (Box-folder 75/7)
    - A, 1951 (Box-folder 75/8)
    - B, 1951 (Box-folder 75/9)
    - Kenneth Curtis, 1951 (Box-folder 75/10)
    - C-D, 1951 (Box-folder 75/11)
    - E-F, 1951 (Box-folder 75/12)
    - Rollo Gullickson, 1951 (Box-folder 76/1)
    - G, 1951 (Box-folder 76/2)
    - H, 1951 (Box-folder 76/3)
    - I-J, 1951 (Box-folder 76/4)
    - K, 1951 (Box-folder 76/5)
    - B. W. Mann, 1951 (Box-folder 76/6)
    - Montana, 1951 (Box-folder 76/7)
    - M, 1951 (Box-folder 76/8)
    - N, 1951 (Box-folder 76/9)
    - O-P, 1951 (Box-folder 76/10)
    - Ravalli County Bank, 1951 (Box-folder 76/11)
    - Regent Can Food Company (Safeway Stores), 1951 (Box-folder 76/12)
    - R, 1951 (Box-folder 76/13)
    - Stone Hall Company, 1951 (Box-folder 76/14)
    - George L. Tracy Company Billings, 1951 (Box-folder 76/15)
    - George L. Tracy Company Butte, 1951 (Box-folder 76/16)
    - George L. Tracy Company Great Falls, 1951 (Box-folder 77/1)
    - George L. Tracy Company Great Falls, 1951 (Box-folder 77/2)
    - United States, 1951 (Box-folder 77/3)
    - S-U, 1951 (Box-folder 77/4)
    - V-W, 1951 (Box-folder 77/5)
    - American Can Company, 1952 (Box-folder 77/6)
    - A, 1952 (Box-folder 77/7)
    - B, 1952 (Box-folder 77/8)
    - Kenneth Curtis, 1952 (Box-folder 77/9)
    - C, 1952 (Box-folder 77/10)
    - D-E, 1952 (Box-folder 77/11)
    - F, 1952 (Box-folder 77/12)
    - G-H, 1952 (Box-folder 78/1)
    - I-K, 1952 (Box-folder 78/2)
    - L, 1952 (Box-folder 78/3)
    - B. W. Mann, 1952 (Box-folder 78/4)
    - Montana, 1952 (Box-folder 78/5)
    - M, 1952 (Box-folder 78/6)
    - N, 1952 (Box-folder 78/7)
    - O-P, 1952 (Box-folder 78/8)
    - Regent Can Food Company (Safeway Stores), 1952 (Box-folder 78/9)
    - R, 1952 (Box-folder 78/10)
    - Stone Hall Company, 1952 (Box-folder 78/11)
    - George L. Tracy Company Billings, 1952 (Box-folder 78/12)
    - George L. Tracy Company Butte, 1952 (Box-folder 78/13)
    - George L. Tracy Company Great Falls, 1952 (Box-folder 78/14)
    - S-T, 1952 (Box-folder 79/1)
    - United States, 1952 (Box-folder 79/2)
    - U-W, 1952 (Box-folder 79/3)
    - American Can Company, 1953 (Box-folder 79/4)
    - A, 1953 (Box-folder 79/5)
    - B, 1953 (Box-folder 79/6)
    - Kenneth Curtis, 1953 (Box-folder 79/7)
    - C, 1953 (Box-folder 79/8)
    - D-E, 1953 (Box-folder 79/9)
    - F, 1953 (Box-folder 79/10)
    - G, 1953 (Box-folder 79/11)
    - H, 1953 (Box-folder 79/12)
    - I-J, 1953 (Box-folder 79/13)
    - K-L, 1953 (Box-folder 79/14)
    - B. W. Mann, 1953 (Box-folder 80/1)
    - Montana, 1953 (Box-folder 80/2)
    - M, 1953 (Box-folder 80/3)
    - N, 1953 (Box-folder 80/4)
    - O-P, 1953 (Box-folder 80/5)
    - Regent Can Food Company (Safeway Stores), 1953 (Box-folder 80/6)
    - Stone Hall Company, 1953 (Box-folder 80/7)
    - R-S, 1953 (Box-folder 80/8)
    - George L. Tracy Company Billings, 1953 (Box-folder 80/9)
    - George L. Tracy Company Butte, 1953 (Box-folder 80/10)
    - George L. Tracy Company Great Falls, 1953 (Box-folder 80/11)
    - United States, 1953 (Box-folder 80/12)
    - T-Y, 1953 (Box-folder 80/13)
    - American Can Company, 1954 (Box-folder 80/14)
    - A, 1954 (Box-folder 80/15)
    - B, 1954 (Box-folder 81/1)
    - Citizens State Bank, 1954 (Box-folder 81/2)
    - Kenneth Curtis, 1954 (Box-folder 81/3)
    - C, 1954 (Box-folder 81/4)
    - D-E, 1954 (Box-folder 81/5)
    - Farmers State Bank, 1954 (Box-folder 81/6)
    - F, 1954 (Box-folder 81/7)
    - Rollo Gullickson, 1954 (Box-folder 81/8)
    - G, 1954 (Box-folder 81/9)
    - H, 1954 (Box-folder 81/10)
    - K-L, 1954 (Box-folder 81/11)
    - M, 1954 (Box-folder 81/12)
    - N, 1954 (Box-folder 81/13)
    - O-P, 1954 (Box-folder 81/14)
    - Regent Can Food Company (Safeway Stores), 1954 (Box-folder 81/15)
    - Stone Hall Company, 1954 (Box-folder 81/16)
    - R-S, 1954 (Box-folder 81/17)
    - George L. Tracy Company Billings, 1954 (Box-folder 81/18)
    - George L. Tracy Company Butte, 1954 (Box-folder 81/19)
    - George L. Tracy Company Great Falls, 1954 (Box-folder 82/1)
    - United States, 1954 (Box-folder 82/2)
    - U-W, 1954 (Box-folder 82/3)
    - American Can Company, 1955 (Box-folder 82/4)
    - A, 1955 (Box-folder 82/5)
    - B, 1955 (Box-folder 82/6)
    - Kenneth Curtis, 1955 (Box-folder 82/7)
    - C, 1955 (Box-folder 82/8)
    - D-E, 1955 (Box-folder 82/9)
    - F, 1955 (Box-folder 82/10)
    - G, 1955 (Box-folder 82/11)
    - The Horsley Company, 1955 (Box-folder 82/12)
    - H-J, 1955 (Box-folder 82/13)
    - K, 1955 (Box-folder 82/14)
    - L, 1955 (Box-folder 83/1)
    - Montana, 1955 (Box-folder 83/2)
    - M, 1955 (Box-folder 83/3)
    - N, 1955 (Box-folder 83/4)
    - O, 1955 (Box-folder 83/5)
    - P, 1955 (Box-folder 83/6)
    - Regent Can Food Company (Safeway Stores), 1955 (Box-folder 83/7)
    - R, 1955 (Box-folder 83/8)
    - Alden Smith, 1955 (Box-folder 83/9)
    - Stone-Hall Company, 1955 (Box-folder 83/10)
    - S, 1955 (Box-folder 83/11)
    - George L. Tracy Company Billings, 1955 (Box-folder 83/12)
    - George L. Tracy Company Butte, 1955 (Box-folder 83/13)
    - George L. Tracy Company Great Falls, 1955 (Box-folder 83/14)
    - United States, 1955 (Box-folder 83/15)
    - T-U, 1955 (Box-folder 83/16)
    - W-Y, 1955 (Box-folder 84/1)
    - American Can Company, 1956 (Box-folder 84/2)
    - A, 1956 (Box-folder 84/3)
    - B, 1956 (Box-folder 84/4)
    - C, 1956 (Box-folder 84/6)
    - D-E, 1956 (Box-folder 84/7)
    - F, 1956 (Box-folder 84/8)
    - Rollo Gullickson, 1956 (Box-folder 84/9)
    - G, 1956 (Box-folder 84/10)
    - The Horsley Company, 1956 (Box-folder 84/11)
    - H-I, 1956 (Box-folder 84/12)
    - James Q. Leavitt Company, 1956 (Box-folder 84/13)
    - K-L, 1956 (Box-folder 84/14)
    - Montana, 1956 (Box-folder 84/15)
    - M, 1956 (Box-folder 84/16)
    - N-O, 1956 (Box-folder 84/17)
    - Regent Can Food Company (Safeway Stores), 1956 (Box-folder 84/18)
    - P-R, 1956 (Box-folder 84/19)
    - Stone-Hall Company, 1956 (Box-folder 85/1)
    - S, 1956 (Box-folder 85/2)
    - George L. Tracy Company Billings, 1956 (Box-folder 85/3)
    - George L. Tracy Company Butte, 1956 (Box-folder 85/4)
    - George L. Tracy Company Great Falls, 1956 (Box-folder 85/5)
    - United States, 1956 (Box-folder 85/6)
    - T-U, 1956 (Box-folder 85/7)
    - V-W, 1956 (Box-folder 85/8)
    - American Can Company, 1957 (Box-folder 85/9)
    - A, 1957 (Box-folder 85/10)
    - B, 1957 (Box-folder 85/11)
    - C, 1957 (Box-folder 85/12)
    - D-E, 1957 (Box-folder 85/13)
    - F, 1957 (Box-folder 85/14)
    - Rollo Gullickson, 1957 (Box-folder 85/15)
    - G, 1957 (Box-folder 85/16)
    - H-I, 1957 (Box-folder 86/1)
    - K, 1957 (Box-folder 86/2)
    - L, 1957 (Box-folder 86/3)
    - Montana, 1957 (Box-folder 86/4)
    - M, 1957 (Box-folder 86/5)
    - N-O, 1957 (Box-folder 86/6)
    - P-R, 1957 (Box-folder 86/7)
    - Stone-Hall Company, 1957 (Box-folder 86/8)
    - S, 1957 (Box-folder 86/9)
    - George L. Tracy Company Billings, 1957 (Box-folder 86/10)
    - George L. Tracy Company Butte, 1957 (Box-folder 86/11)
    - George L. Tracy Company Great Falls, 1957 (Box-folder 86/12)
    - T, 1957 (Box-folder 86/13)
    - United States, 1957 (Box-folder 86/14)
    - V-W, 1957 (Box-folder 86/15)
    - A-B, 1958 (Box-folder 86/16)
    - F. M. Carriere and Son, 1958 (Box-folder 87/1)
    - Otto W. Cuyler Corporation, 1958 (Box-folder 87/2)
    - C, 1958 (Box-folder 87/3)
    - E-F, 1958 (Box-folder 87/4)
    - G-H, 1958 (Box-folder 87/5)
    - K-L, 1958 (Box-folder 87/6)
    - Montana, 1958 (Box-folder 87/7)
    - M, 1958 (Box-folder 87/8)
    - Eugene O'Neill, 1958 (Box-folder 87/9)
    - N-P, 1958 (Box-folder 87/10)
    - Regent Can Food Company (Safeway Stores), 1958 (Box-folder 87/11)
    - Stone-Hall Company, 1958 (Box-folder 87/12)
    - R-S, 1958 (Box-folder 87/13)
    - George L. Tracy Company Billings, 1958 (Box-folder 87/14)
    - George L. Tracy Company Butte, 1958 (Box-folder 87/15)
    - George L. Tracy Company Great Falls, 1958 (Box-folder 88/1)
    - United States, 1958 (Box-folder 88/2)
    - T-W, 1958 (Box-folder 88/3)
    - A, 1959 (Box-folder 88/4)
    - Big Stone Canning Company, 1959 (Box-folder 88/5)
    - B, 1959 (Box-folder 88/6)
    - C-F, 1959 (Box-folder 88/7)
    - Mike Mansfield, 1959 (Box-folder 88/8)
    - Lee Metcalf, 1959 (Box-folder 88/9)
    - Montana, 1959 (Box-folder 88/10)
    - James E. Murray, 1959 (Box-folder 88/11)
    - George L. Tracy Company, 1959 (Box-folder 88/12)
    - G-W, 1959 (Box-folder 88/13)
    - Big Horn Canning Company, 1960 (Box-folder 88/14)
    - Big Stone Canning Company, 1960 (Box-folder 88/15)
    - Big Stone Canning Company, 1960 (Box-folder 88/16)
    - A-C, 1960 (Box-folder 88/17)
    - Gallatin Valley Seed Company, 1960 (Box-folder 88/18)
    - D-G, 1960 (Box-folder 89/1)
    - Jensen Sales Company, 1960 (Box-folder 89/2)
    - H-L, 1960 (Box-folder 89/3)
    - Montana, 1960 (Box-folder 89/4)
    - M-R, 1960 (Box-folder 89/5)
    - Stone-Hall Company, 1960 (Box-folder 89/6)
    - George L. Tracy Company, 1960 (Box-folder 89/7)
    - S-Z, 1960 (Box-folder 89/8)
    - Big Stone Canning Company, 1961 (Box-folder 89/9)
    - A-C, 1961 (Box-folder 89/10)
    - D-G, 1961 (Box-folder 89/11)
    - H-I, 1961 (Box-folder 89/12)
    - J-K, 1961 (Box-folder 89/13)
    - L-M, 1961 (Box-folder 89/14)
    - N-P, 1961 (Box-folder 89/15)
    - George L. Tracy Company, 1961 (Box-folder 89/16)
    - Water Resources Development Corporation, 1961 (Box-folder 90/1)
    - R-W, 1961 (Box-folder 90/2)
    - A-Z, 1962 (Box-folder 90/3)
    - A, 1963 (Box-folder 90/4)
    - Big Stone Canning Company, 1963 (Box-folder 90/5)
    - Big Stone Canning Company, 1963 (Box-folder 90/6)
    - B, 1963 (Box-folder 90/7)
    - Continental Can Company, 1963 (Box-folder 90/8)
    - C, 1963 (Box-folder 90/9)
    - D, 1963 (Box-folder 90/10)
    - E, 1963 (Box-folder 90/11)
    - F, 1963 (Box-folder 90/12)
    - G, 1963 (Box-folder 90/13)
    - H-I, 1963 (Box-folder 90/14)
    - J, 1963 (Box-folder 90/15)
    - K, 1963 (Box-folder 90/16)
    - L, 1963 (Box-folder 90/17)
    - Montana, 1963 (Box-folder 90/18)
    - M, 1963 (Box-folder 90/19)
    - N, 1963 (Box-folder 91/1)
    - O, 1963 (Box-folder 91/2)
    - P, 1963 (Box-folder 91/3)
    - R, 1963 (Box-folder 91/4)
    - Stone-Hall Company, 1963 (Box-folder 91/5)
    - S, 1963 (Box-folder 91/6)
    - United States, 1963 (Box-folder 91/7)
    - U, 1963 (Box-folder 91/8)
    - W, 1963 (Box-folder 91/9)
    - Y, 1963 (Box-folder 91/10)
    - A, 1964 (Box-folder 91/11)
    - Big Horn Canning Company, 1964 (Box-folder 91/12)
    - Big Stone Canning Company, 1964 (Box-folder 91/13)
    - Big Horn Canning Company, 1964 (Box-folder 91/14)
    - Big Horn Canning Company, 1964 (Box-folder 91/15)
    - B, 1964 (Box-folder 91/16)
    - C, 1964 (Box-folder 91/17)
    - D, 1964 (Box-folder 92/1)
    - E, 1964 (Box-folder 92/2)
    - F, 1964 (Box-folder 92/3)
    - G-H, 1964 (Box-folder 92/4)
    - Jensen Sales Company, 1964 (Box-folder 92/5)
    - I-J, 1964 (Box-folder 92/6)
    - K, 1964 (Box-folder 92/7)
    - L, 1964 (Box-folder 92/8)
    - Montana, 1964 (Box-folder 92/9)
    - M, 1964 (Box-folder 92/10)
    - Northrup, King and Company, 1964 (Box-folder 92/11)
    - N, 1964 (Box-folder 92/12)
    - P, 1964 (Box-folder 92/13)
    - Ryan Grocery Company Billings, 1964 (Box-folder 92/14)
    - R, 1964 (Box-folder 92/15)
    - Stone-Hall Company, 1964 (Box-folder 92/16)
    - S, 1964 (Box-folder 92/17)
    - United States, 1964 (Box-folder 92/18)
    - T-V, 1964 (Box-folder 92/19)
    - W, 1964 (Box-folder 92/20)
    - Y-Z, 1964 (Box-folder 92/21)
    - James Battin, 1965 (Box-folder 92/22)
    - Big Stone Canning Company, 1965 (Box-folder 92/23)
    - A-B, 1965 (Box-folder 92/24)
    - C, 1965 (Box-folder 92/25)
    - D, 1965 (Box-folder 92/26)
    - E-G, 1965 (Box-folder 92/27)
    - H-K, 1965 (Box-folder 93/1)
    - Mike Mansfield, 1965 (Box-folder 93/2)
    - Lee Metcalf, 1965 (Box-folder 93/3)
    - Montana, 1965 (Box-folder 93/4)
    - M, 1965 (Box-folder 93/5)
    - N-P, 1965 (Box-folder 93/6)
    - R-S, 1965 (Box-folder 93/7)
    - United States, 1965 (Box-folder 93/8)
    - T-W, 1965 (Box-folder 93/9)
    - Big Stone Canning Company, 1966 (Box-folder 93/10)
    - A-B, 1966 (Box-folder 93/11)
    - C, 1966 (Box-folder 93/12)
    - D-E, 1966 (Box-folder 93/13)
    - F, 1966 (Box-folder 93/14)
    - G-I, 1966 (Box-folder 93/15)
    - J-L, 1966 (Box-folder 93/16)
    - M, 1966 (Box-folder 93/17)
    - N-O, 1966 (Box-folder 93/18)
    - P, 1966 (Box-folder 93/19)
    - R, 1966 (Box-folder 94/1)
    - Stone-Hall Company, 1966 (Box-folder 94/2)
    - United States, 1966 (Box-folder 94/3)
    - S-U, 1966 (Box-folder 94/4)
    - W, 1966 (Box-folder 94/5)
    - Z, 1966 (Box-folder 94/6)
    - James Battin, 1967 (Box-folder 94/7)
    - Big Stone Canning Company, 1967 (Box-folder 94/8)
    - B, 1967 (Box-folder 94/9)
    - C-E, 1967 (Box-folder 94/10)
    - F-I, 1967 (Box-folder 94/11)
    - Jensen Sales Company, 1967 (Box-folder 94/12)
    - J-L, 1967 (Box-folder 94/13)
    - Montana, 1967 (Box-folder 94/14)
    - M, 1967 (Box-folder 94/15)
    - Arnold Olsen, 1967 (Box-folder 94/16)
    - N-O, 1967 (Box-folder 94/17)
    - P, 1967 (Box-folder 94/18)
    - Rocky Mountain Canners Association, 1967 (Box-folder 94/19)
    - F. C. Roehl and Company, 1967 (Box-folder 94/20)
    - Stone-Hall Company, 1967 (Box-folder 94/21)
    - R-T, 1967 (Box-folder 94/22)
    - United States, 1967 (Box-folder 94/23)
    - U-W, 1967 (Box-folder 94/24)
    - James Battin, 1968 (Box-folder 94/25)
    - Beacon Sales Company, 1968 (Box-folder 94/26)
    - Big Horn Canning Company, 1968 (Box-folder 95/1)
    - Big Stone Canning Company, 1968 (Box-folder 95/2)
    - Big Stone Canning Company, 1968 (Box-folder 95/3)
    - A-B, 1968 (Box-folder 95/4)
    - Patrick Dougherty, 1968 (Box-folder 95/5)
    - C-D, 1968 (Box-folder 95/6)
    - E, 1968 (Box-folder 95/7)
    - Fairbanks-Peaslee Company, 1968 (Box-folder 95/8)
    - F-L, 1968 (Box-folder 95/9)
    - Mike Mansfield, 1968 (Box-folder 95/10)
    - Lee Metcalf, 1968 (Box-folder 95/11)
    - Montana, 1968 (Box-folder 95/12)
    - M-N, 1968 (Box-folder 95/13)
    - Arnold Olsen, 1968 (Box-folder 95/14)
    - O-R, 1968 (Box-folder 95/15)
    - R, 1968 (Box-folder 95/16)
    - Stone-Hall Company, 1968 (Box-folder 95/17)
    - United States, 1968 (Box-folder 95/18)
    - S-Y, 1968 (Box-folder 95/19)
    - Beacon Sales Company, 1968 (Box-folder 95/20)
    - Big Horn Canning Company, 1969 (Box-folder 96/1)
    - Big Stone Canning Company, 1969 (Box-folder 96/2)
    - Big Stone Canning Company, 1969 (Box-folder 96/3)
    - A-C, 1969 (Box-folder 96/4)
    - Patrick Dougherty, 1969 (Box-folder 96/5)
    - Fairbanks-Peaslee, 1969 (Box-folder 96/6)
    - D-H, 1969 (Box-folder 96/7)
    - I-K, 1969 (Box-folder 96/8)
    - Mike Mansfield, 1969 (Box-folder 96/9)
    - Lee Metcalf, 1969 (Box-folder 96/10)
    - Montana, 1969 (Box-folder 96/11)
    - L-M, 1969 (Box-folder 96/12)
    - Arnold Olsen, 1969 (Box-folder 96/13)
    - N-P, 1969 (Box-folder 96/14)
    - R, 1969 (Box-folder 96/15)
    - Stone-Hall Company, 1969 (Box-folder 96/16)
    - S, 1969 (Box-folder 96/17)
    - United States, 1969 (Box-folder 96/18)
    - T-Z, 1969 (Box-folder 96/19)
    - Big Stone Canning Company, 1970 (Box-folder 96/20)
    - A-E, 1970 (Box-folder 97/1)
    - F-L, 1970 (Box-folder 97/2)
    - Montana, 1970 (Box-folder 97/3)
    - M-R, 1970 (Box-folder 97/4)
    - Stone-Hall Company, 1970 (Box-folder 97/5)
    - United States, 1970 (Box-folder 97/6)
    - S-Z, 1970 (Box-folder 97/7)
    - Mike Mansfield, 1971 (Box-folder 97/8)
    - John Melcher, 1971 (Box-folder 97/9)
    - Lee Metcalf, 1971 (Box-folder 97/10)
    - Montana, 1971 (Box-folder 97/11)
    - United States, 1971 (Box-folder 97/12)
    - A-Z, 1971 (Box-folder 97/13)
    - Big Stone Canning Company, 1972 (Box-folder 97/14)
    - Big Stone Canning Company, 1972 (Box-folder 97/15)
    - A-G, 1972 (Box-folder 97/16)
    - Mike Mansfield, 1972 (Box-folder 97/17)
    - John Melcher, 1972 (Box-folder 97/18)
    - Lee Metcalf, 1972 (Box-folder 97/19)
    - Montana, 1972 (Box-folder 97/20)
    - H-O, 1972 (Box-folder 97/21)
    - Richard Shoup, 1972 (Box-folder 98/1)
    - United States, 1972 (Box-folder 98/2)
    - P-Z, 1972 (Box-folder 98/3)
    - Big Stone Canning Company, 1973 (Box-folder 98/4)
    - A-B, 1973 (Box-folder 98/5)
    - C-E, 1973 (Box-folder 98/6)
    - F-I, 1973 (Box-folder 98/7)
    - John Melcher, 1973 (Box-folder 98/8)
    - Montana, 1973 (Box-folder 98/9)
    - J-N, 1973 (Box-folder 98/10)
    - Richard Shoup, 1973 (Box-folder 98/11)
    - United States, 1973 (Box-folder 98/12)
    - O-Z, 1973 (Box-folder 98/13)
    - Big Stone Canning Company, 1974 (Box-folder 98/14)
    - Mike Mansfield, 1974 (Box-folder 98/15)
    - John Melcher, 1974 (Box-folder 98/16)
    - Lee Kletcalf, 1974 (Box-folder 98/17)
    - Montana, 1974 (Box-folder 98/18)
    - Richard Shoup, 1974 (Box-folder 98/19)
    - A-Z, 1974 (Box-folder 98/20)
  - Interoffice Correspondence, 1926-1974; Subseries 2; 2.25 linear feet
    - January-August, 1926 (Box-folder 99/1)
    - September-December, 1926 (Box-folder 99/2)
    - January-June, 1927 (Box-folder 99/3)
    - July-December, 1927 (Box-folder 99/4)
    - 1928 (Box-folder 99/5)
    - 1929 (Box-folder 99/6)
    - 1930 (Box-folder 99/7)
    - 1931 (Box-folder 99/8)
    - 1934 (Box-folder 99/9)
    - 1938 (Box-folder 100/1)
    - Bitters, H. E., 1939 (Box-folder 100/2)
    - 1939 (Box-folder 100/3)
    - Bitters, H. E., 1940 (Box-folder 100/4)
    - Mann, M. H., 1940 (Box-folder 100/5)
    - Stevensville Cannery, 1940 (Box-folder 100/6)
    - Stevensville Cannery, 1940 (Box-folder 100/7)
    - January-May, 1941 (Box-folder 100/8)
    - June-September, 1941 (Box-folder 101/1)
    - October-December, 1941 (Box-folder 101/2)
    - January-May, 1942 (Box-folder 101/3)
    - June-December, 1942 (Box-folder 101/4)
    - 1943 (Box-folder 101/5)
    - Stevensville, 1944 (Box-folder 101/6)
    - 1944 (Box-folder 101/7)
    - 1946 (Box-folder 102/1)
    - 1947 (Box-folder 102/2)
    - 1948 (Box-folder 102/3)
    - 1949 (Box-folder 102/4)
    - 1950 (Box-folder 102/5)
    - 1951 (Box-folder 102/6)
    - 1952 (Box-folder 102/7)
    - 1953 (Box-folder 102/8)
    - 1954 (Box-folder 103/1)
    - 1955 (Box-folder 103/2)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 103/3)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 103/4)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 103/5)
    - 1972 (Box-folder 103/6)
    - 1973 (Box-folder 103/7)
    - 1974 (Box-folder 103/8)
- Financial, 1926-1969; Series II; 0.75 linear feet
  This series contains production statements, account records, and asset statements from the Red Lodge Canning Company.
  - 1926 (Box-folder 104/1)
  - 1927 (Box-folder 104/2)
  - 1929 (Box-folder 104/3)
  - 1930 (Box-folder 104/4)
  - 1931 (Box-folder 104/5)
  - 1937 (Box-folder 104/6)
  - 1938 (Box-folder 104/7)
  - 1939 (Box-folder 104/8)
  - 1940 (Box-folder 104/9)
  - 1941 (Box-folder 104/10)
  - 1942 (Box-folder 104/11)
  - 1943 (Box-folder 104/12)
  - 1944 (Box-folder 104/13)
  - 1945 (Box-folder 104/14)
  - 1946 (Box-folder 104/15)
  - 1947 (Box-folder 104/16)
  - 1948 (Box-folder 104/17)
  - 1949 (Box-folder 104/18)
  - 1950 (Box-folder 104/19)
  - 1951 (Box-folder 105/1)
  - 1952 (Box-folder 105/2)
  - 1953 (Box-folder 105/3)
  - 1954 (Box-folder 105/4)
  - 1955 (Box-folder 105/5)
  - 1957 (Box-folder 105/6)
  - 1958 (Box-folder 105/7)
  - 1959 (Box-folder 105/8)
  - 1961 (Box-folder 105/9)
  - 1962 (Box-folder 105/10)
  - 1963 (Box-folder 105/11)
  - 1964 (Box-folder 105/12)
  - 1966 (Box-folder 105/13)
  - 1967 (Box-folder 105/14)
  - 1968 (Box-folder 105/15)
  - 1969 (Box-folder 105/16)
  - Record of Production, 1926-1957 (Volume 1)
  - General Ledger, 1937-1939, 1951, 1954 (Volume 2)
  - Growers Ledger, 1938-1940, 1942-1954, 1956-1958 (Volume 3)
  - Sales Ledger, 1937-1956 (Volume 4)
  - Payroll 1926-1927; Raw Materials Purchased 1926; Check Register, 1937-1957 (Volume 5)
- Legal, 1926-1972; Series III; 0.75 linear feet
  This series contains purchase agreements, operational licenses, equipment lease agreements, and distribution contracts from the Red Lodge Canning Company.
  - 1926 (Box-folder 105/17)
  - 1927 (Box-folder 105/18)
  - 1928 (Box-folder 105/19)
  - 1929 (Box-folder 105/20)
  - 1931 (Box-folder 105/21)
  - 1932 (Box-folder 106/1)
  - 1933 (Box-folder 106/2)
  - 1936 (Box-folder 106/3)
  - 1937 (Box-folder 106/4)
  - 1939 (Box-folder 106/5)
  - 1940 (Box-folder 106/6)
  - 1941 (Box-folder 106/7)
  - 1942 (Box-folder 106/8)
  - 1943 (Box-folder 106/9)
  - 1944 (Box-folder 106/10)
  - 1945 (Box-folder 106/11)
  - 1947 (Box-folder 106/12)
  - 1949 (Box-folder 106/13)
  - 1951 (Box-folder 106/14)
  - 1952 (Box-folder 106/15)
  - 1953 (Box-folder 106/16)
  - 1954 (Box-folder 106/17)
  - 1955 (Box-folder 106/18)
  - Growers Contracts, 1965 (Box-folder 106/19)
  - 1972 (Box-folder 106/20)
- Organization, 1926-1972; Series IV; 1.0 linear feet
  This series contains stockholder information and board minutes from the Red Lodge Canning Company.
  - 1926 (Box-folder 106/21)
  - 1927 (Box-folder 106/22)
  - 1930 (Box-folder 106/23)
  - 1934 (Box-folder 106/24)
  - 1936 (Box-folder 107/1)
  - 1937 (Box-folder 107/2)
  - 1938 (Box-folder 107/3)
  - 1939 (Box-folder 107/4)
  - 1940 (Box-folder 107/5)
  - 1941 (Box-folder 107/6)
  - 1942 (Box-folder 107/7)
  - 1943 (Box-folder 107/8)
  - 1944 (Box-folder 107/9)
  - 1945 (Box-folder 107/10)
  - 1946 (Box-folder 107/11)
  - 1947 (Box-folder 107/12)
  - 1968 (Box-folder 107/13)
  - 1969 (Box-folder 107/14)
  - 1972 (Box-folder 107/15)
  - Stock Certificates, 1926 (Box-folder 107/16)
  - Stock Certificates, 1926 (Box-folder 107/17)
  - Stock Certificates, 1926 (Box-folder 108/1)
  - Stock Certificates, 1926 (Box-folder 108/2)
  - Stock Certificates, 1939 (Box-folder 108/3)
- Printed Materials, 1922-1943; Series V; 0.75 linear feet